<resources>
	<string name="app_name">Seguime</string>

	<string name="Traducidopor">Javier</string>

	<string name="menu_abrir">Menú</string>
	<string name="menu_cerrar">Close Menú</string>

	<string name="servidor">Server</string>
	<string name="usuario">User</string>
	<string name="clave">Password</string>
	<string name="intervalo_inactividad">Idle interval (in minutes)</string>
	<string name="intervalo_actividad">Activity interval (in minutes)</string>
	<string name="sms">SMS</string>
	<string name="id_telegram">Chat_ID Telegram (NO @USER_ID)</string>
	<string name="rastreo">Tracking (send messages)</string>
    <string name="telegram_bot">Telegram BOT</string>
	<string name="iniciarConElSistema">Start on boot</string>
	<string name="errorValidacion">There is an error</string>


    <string name="espere">Please wait... ️</string>

	<string name="sesion_clavedesigual">Repeat password</string>
	<string name="sesion_clavecorta">Password is too short</string>
	<string name="sesion_usuariocorto">User name is too short</string>
	<string name="sesion_sinservidor">Need a url server</string>

	<string name="cerrarsesion_mensajeadvertencia">All data will be erased. Are you sure?</string>

	<string name="latitud">Latitude</string>
	<string name="longitud">Longitude</string>
	<string name="fechahora">Date and Time</string>
	<string name="fecha">Date</string>
	<string name="hora">Time</string>
	<string name="Infoextra">Extra Info</string>

	<string name="contactos">Contacts</string>
	
	
	<string name="configuracion">Settings</string>
	<string name="opciones">Options</string>
	<string name="guardar">Save</string>
	<string name="cancelar">Cancel</string>
	<string name="editar">Edit</string>
	<string name="registros">Records</string>
	<string name="cerrar_sesion">Logoff</string>
	<string name="salir">Exit</string>

	<string name="velocidad">Speed</string>
	
		
	<string name="txt_bloqueado_alarma">Service can not be stoped when there is an countdown alarm activated</string>
	<string name="alarma">Alarm (Alert Message)</string>
	<string name="alarmamensaje">May be I need help, try contact to me now!</string>
	<string name="iniciar">Start</string>
	<string name="detener">Stop</string>
	<string name="mensajealerta">Alert Message</string>

	<string name="minuto">Minute</string>
	<string name="segundo">Second</string>

	<string name="principal_alarma">alarm activated</string>
	<string name="principal_rastreo">Tracking activated</string>
	<string name="principal_aplicacion">This application is activated</string>
	<string name="principal_internet">There is an internet connection</string>
    <string name="principal_alarmaservidor">There is a alarm copy on server</string>

	
	
	<string name="txt_servicio_activo">Nice! The application is enabled:-)</string>
	<string name="txt_servicio_inactivo">The application is disabled, press the button to activate it</string>
	<string name="txt_bloqueado">At this time the application is locked</string>

	<string name="activar_aplicacion">¡Seguime!</string>
	<string name="desactivar_aplicacion">No me sigas</string>

	
	<string name="cuentaregresiva">Countdown</string>
	
	<string name="ayuda">Help</string>
	<string name="cerrar">close</string>

	
	
		
	
	
	<string name="iniciarsesion">login</string>
	<string name="registrarse">join in</string>
	<string name="repetirclave">Repeat password (do not use real passwords)</string>
	<string name="ssl">Secure Connection SSL</string>


	<string name="registrarAplicacion">Register Version</string>
	<string name="nombre">Name</string>
	<string name="versionRegistrada">Registered Version</string>
    <string name="claveIncorrecta">Wrong Password</string>
	<string name="requiereregistro">Registered version is required</string>
	<string name="txt_registrodeversion">Register is free, get you key on website, personal information is not required</string>


	<string name="conectando">Connecting...</string>
	<string name="errorconexion">Connection Error</string>
	<string name="enviano">Sending data....</string>
	<string name="recibiendo">Receiving data...</string>
	<string name="conexionfinalizada">Correct connection... but nothing happened.</string>



    <string name="presentacion_dispositivo">Encontrá tu dispositivo</string>
    <string name="presentacion_servidor">Usá tu propio Serviddor</string>
    <string name="presentacion_alerta">Enviá mensajes de alerta</string>
    <string name="presentacion_remoto">Configurá la aplicación de forma remota</string>




    <string name="txt_ayuda_descripcion">
		Seguime te permite rastrear tu dispositivo, 
		recolecta información del GPS y la almacena para luego poder enviarlas a tu servidor.
		Desde el servidor se puede ver los registros en un mapa y ver donde esta (o estuvo) el dispositivo.
		El servidor puede ser el de un amigo, familiar o el tuyo, 
		podes montar tu propio servidor para mayor privacidad de tus datos.
		Además incluye un temporizador que te permite programar en que momento la aplicación activará su modo de rastreo 
		y adicionalmente enviar un mensaje de ayuda.
		Cuando la aplicación esta en modo de rastreo enviara por SMS o Telegram mensajes con la ubicación.
	</string>
	
	<string name="txt_advertencia_proyecto">
		This is a project, it is not (and not pretends to be) a security application,
		it is only for experimental use.
		The developer (or developers and collaborators) 
		are not and will not be responsible for the use or misure of these programs
		(applications, website, source codes, etc.).
	
		Esto es un proyecto, no es (ni prende ser) una aplicación de seguridad, 
		es solo para uso experimental.
		El desarrollador (o desarrolladores y colaboradores) 
		no son ni serán responsables por el uso o mal uso de estos programas 
		(aplicaciones, sitio web, códigos fuentes, etc.).
	</string>
	
	

	<string name="txt_licencia">This program is free software: You can redistribute it and/or modify
	It under the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by
	The Free Software Foundation, either version 3 of the License, or
	(at your option) any later version. \n

	This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
	But WITHOUT ANY warranty; Without even the implied warranty of
	MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS for A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. See the
	GNU General Public License for more details. \n

	You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License
	Along with this program. If not, see http://www.gnu.org/licenses/
	</string>

		
	
	
	<string name="dona">Make a donation:)</string>
	<string name="sitioweb">Go to Web site</string>
	<string name="txt_donacion">If you like the application you can collaborate with a donation. \n
	Remember that this application has no publicity, no sponsor, no trackers, so it depends solely on the collaboration of users.

	</string>

	<string name="txt_ayuda_opciones">You will see that it is not so complicated, you have the following options: \n
	\n

	SMS: \n
	It is a phone number that you can choose for the application to send coordinates by SMS. \n
	SMS will only be sent if the tracking option is enabled. \n
	To avoid expenses I recommend not using this option if you are using the Seguime server, use this option only if you are using your own server, or a secure server \n
	\n
	Telegram ID: \n
	is a number identifier of Telegram, is not the @ID_USUARIO, to use this option visit the bot @seguimebot and greet it, will give you your ID number, then with that number the bot can send coordinates to that account Telegram. \n
	\n
	Activity range: \n
	During this period the application will be working completely, locating coordinates and making connections to Internet, a very small value may not achieve coordinates if you have little GPS coverage, a very high value can consume a lot of battery \n
	For the application to be constantly on (and not for time intervals) set any time interval to 0 (zero) \n
	\n
	Idle interval: \n
	During this period the application will be resting, do not make Internet connections or locate coordinates, a rest is used to save battery, a very small value may consume a lot of battery, a very high value will hinder the purpose of the Application \n
	For the application to be constantly on (and not for time intervals) set any time interval to 0 (zero) \n
	\n
	Tracking: \n
	When this option is enabled the application will send messages by Telegram and SMS each time you find a new coordinate. This option can be enabled from the Web site therefore for your security and to avoid expenses do not configure SMS unless you are using your own server \n
	\n
	\n
	I hope you can use this help
	\n
	\n
	\n

	</string>

	
	
	<string name="txt_ayuda_regresiva">
        Ayuda del temporizador: \n
		\n
		Te permite programar una cuenta regresiva, una vez activada hará lo siguiente: \n
		1. Configurara el numero de teléfono para enviar mensajes de texto. \n
		2. Dejara la aplicación en modo activado, solo se podrá desactivar la aplicación si no hay temporizadores programados. \n
		3. Enviara una copia de la cuenta regresiva al servidor. \n
		 \n
		Al finalizar la cuenta regresiva activara una alarma que hará lo siguiente: \n
		1. Pondrá la aplicación en modo de rastreo. \n
		2. Enviara un SMS programado con el texto elegido. \n
		3. El servidor enviara mensajes por Telegram.  \n
		 \n
	</string>


	
	
	<string name="txt_firma">
        Made in Argentina by Javier Martínez
    </string>    
	
	
	
</resources>